Finding Aid for the Joseph Byrne Lockey Papers LSC.0127
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Central America
  - 23. Notes (Miscellaneous)
    - Molina, Luis to His Excellency J.S. Black. Washington, December 26, 1860.; 34.; 16pp. (Copy, typewritten, of notes from Central American Legations, vol.4). (Box 2)
    - Molina, Luis to His Excellency, William H. Seward. Legations of Costa Rica, Nicaragua and Honduras. Washington, April 4, 1861.; 35.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of notes from Central American Legations, vol.4). (Box 2)
  - 24. Transit
    - Newspaper article, The Nicaragua Transit Company Route. To the American Public., 1.; Copy, photostat, of Foreign Office 5/558. 8.5 × 14 paper. 1p. (Box 2)
    - Newspaper article, no title, including several letters. Last Signature, J.L. White., 2.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of Foreign Office 5/548 - 8.5 × 14 paper). (Box 2)
    - Newspaper article, no title, including several letters. Last item - Protest from Legation of the Republic of Nicaragua., 3.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of Foreign Office 5/548 - 8.5 × 11 paper). (Box 2)
  - 25. Treaties, British with Central American Nations
    - Treaty Series no.11, Convention and Protocol between Great Britain and Nicaragua for the Settlement of Certain Claims Arising out of the Disturbances in the Mosquito Reserve in 1894. Signed at London, 1896. November 1, 1895.; 1.; 8pp. printed. Blue paper cover. (Box 2)
    - Palmerston and the Clayton-Bulwer Treaty. G.F. Hickson. vol.3 no.3, 1931.; 2.; 12pp. printed. Blue paper cover. (Box 2)
    - Treaty of Friendship, Commerce, and Navigation between Her Majesty and the Republick of Guatemala. Signed at Guatemala, February 20, 1849.; 3.; 10pp. printed. (Box 2)
    - Convention between Her Majesty and the Republic of Guatemala relative to the Boundary of British Honduras. Signed at Guatemala, April 30, 1859.; 4.; 3pp. printed. (Box 2)
    - Treaty of Friendship, Commerce, and Navigation between Her Majesty and the Republic of Honduras with an additional Article Thereunto Annexed. Signed at London, August 27, 1856.; 5.; 11pp. printed. (Box 2)
    - Treaty of Friendship, Commerce, and Navigation between Her Majesty and the Republic of Nicaragua. Signed at Managua, February 11, 1860.; 6.; 12pp. printed. (Box 2)
    - Treaty between Her Majesty and the Republic of Nicaragua, Relative to the Mosquito Indians, and to the Rights and Claims of British Subjects. Signed at Managua, January 28, 1860.; 7.; 7pp. printed. (Box 2)
    - Further Correspondence with the United States Respecting Central America, 1856.; 8.; 19pp. printed. (Box 2)
    - Treaty of Friendship, Commerce, and Navigation between Her Majesty and the Republick of Costa Rica. Signed at San Jose, November 27, 1849.; 9.; 11pp. printed. (Box 2)
  - 26. Alston
    - Alston, Francis Beilby - Francis Beilby Alston's Report on Central America. Foreign Office, July 20, 1859.; 1.; 22pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/107 - 7 × 9 red margin paper).
  - 27. Barrundia
    - Crampton to Clarendon. Washington, June 5, 1854.; 1.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/596 - 7 × 9 red margin paper).
      - Enclosure to Foreign Office 5/596, June 1854.; 1.; 1p. Photostatic copy of extract from the Union. 8.5 × 14 paper.
  - 28. Beelen
    - Beelen, Fred A. to Honorable William L. Marcy. Diplomatic Bureau, Department of State, Washington, July 15, 1854.; 1.; 3pp. (Photostatic copy).
  - 29. Berendt
    - Berendt, D.C. to Mr. Frank Squier. Coban, April 15, 1878.; 1.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers).
    - Berendt, D.C. to Frank Squier. New York, December 22, 1876.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers).
  - 30. Borland
    - Bozland to Marcy, August 28, 1853.; 1.; 13pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. no.3).
    - Bozland to Marcy, October 8, 1853.; 2.; 6pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. no.6).
    - No Name., 3.; 9pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Marcy Papers).
  - 31. Buchanan
    - Buchanan to Marcy, January 22, 1856.; 1.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. no.114).
    - Buchanan to Marcy, February 1, 1856.; 2.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. no.117).
  - 32. Bulwer
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, June 1, 1850.; 1.; 10pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/511 no.5 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, January 6, 1850.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/511 no.12 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, January 21, 1850.; 3.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/511 no.19 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, Foreign Office, 5/512 no.43., March 2, 1850.; 4.; Copy, typewritten, 7 × 9 red margin paper. 3pp. (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, March 2, 1850.; 5.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/512 no.46). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, March 16, 1850.; 6.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/512 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, May 6, 1850.; 7.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/512 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, June 3, 1850.; 8.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/513 no.92). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston, Washington, June 17, 1850.; 9.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/513 - Extract - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Green. Washington, June 29, 1850.; 10.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 53/23 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, August 6, 1850.; 11.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/514 no.157 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, September 23, 1850.; 12.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/530 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, September 23, 1850.; 13.; (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/515 no.189.) (7 × 9 red margin paper). 2pp. (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, September 29, 1850.; 14.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/515 no.199 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, September 29, 1850.; 15.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/515, no.200) (7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Webster to Bulwer. Department of State, September 24, 1850.; 16.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/515). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, October 7, 1850.; 17.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/515 no.209 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Charfield, Washington, December 15, 1850.; 18.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Bulwer to Chatfield, Extracts from Foreign Office 5/527). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, January 28, 1851.; 19.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/527 no.20 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, March 24, 1851.; 20.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/528 no.54 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston, Washington, April 7, 1851.; 21.; (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/528. no.71 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). 2pp. (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. New York, August 2, 1851.; 22.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/529. no.136 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. New York, August 12, 1851.; 23.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/529 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - [Bulwer] Copy of letters and so forth secretly communicated to me by the Right Honorable Sir H. Lytton Bulwer, Translated abstracts of two letters written in Nicaragua in The receiver is not identified., February 27, 1850. December 1849.; 24.; 7pp. (Copy, photostat - 8.5 × 11.75. State Department(?). (Box 2)
    - Bulwer, H.L. to [Unknown]. Washington, January 3, 1850.; 25.; 3pp. [Copy, photostat, of State Department(?) - 11.75 × 8.5 paper]. (Box 2)
    - Bulwer, H.L. to [Unknown]. Washington, February 14, 1850.; 26.; 10pp. [Copy, photostat, of State Department(?) - 11.75 × 8.5 paper]. (Box 2)
    - Bulwer, H.L. to [Unknown]. Washington, February 15, 1850.; 27.; 2pp. [Copy, photostat, of archive? - 11.75 × 8.5 paper]. (Box 2)
    - Bulwer, H.L. to [Unknown]. Washington, September 24, 1850.; 28.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of Archive - 11.75 × 8.5 paper). (Box 2)
    - Ward, J.D. Sir Henry Bulver and the United States Archives, 1931.; 29.; 10pp. (6.25 × 9 - blue cover, booklet, printed). (Box 2)
  - 33. Cass
    - Cass, Lewis to Lord Napier, May 29, 1857.; 1.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department writings). (Box 2)
    - Cass to Dallas, April 7, 1859.; 2.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department writings). (Box 2)
    - Cass to Dallas, August 12, 1859.; 3.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department writings). (Box 2)
  - 34. Castlereagh
    - Castlereigh, Viscount to Sir Henry Wellesley. Foreign Office, January 10, 1817.; 1.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 72/196).
  - 35. Chatfield
    - Chatfield, Fred to Palmerston. Guatemala, January 28, 1847.; 1.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/43 - January 28, 1847.) (7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield, Fred to Palmerston. Guatemala, January 29, 1847.; 2.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/45 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield, Fred to the Right Honourable Viscount Palmerston, K.B. Guatemala, June 28, 1847.; 3.; 6pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/46 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield, Fred to The Right Honourable Viscount Palmerston, K.B. Guatemala, July 14, 1847.; 4.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/46 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Seymour to Henderson.H.M. Ship Collingwood, Valparaiso, October 1, 1847.; 5.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/47 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Henderson to Chatfield, H.M. Steam Ship Sampson, Istapa, December 17, 1847.; 6.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/47 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, December 20, 1847.; 7.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/47 no.62 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, March 7, 1848.; 8.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 252/38 no.29 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield, to Palmerston, March 28, 1848.; 9.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 252/38. no.35 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, Foreign Office, December 15, 1848.; 10.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/53 no.116 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, January 12, 1849.; 11.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/57 no.6 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, H.M.S. Gorgon Union, November 7, 1849.; 12.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/60 no.107 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, San Jose, And extract of a letter from Mr. Charles Booth dated New York, December 15, 1849. September 4, 1849.; 13.; 6pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/60, no.119 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, San Jose, December 15, 1849.; 14.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/60, no.120. 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, San Jose, January 29, 1850.; 15.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/64, no.22 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, San Jose de Costarica, March 2, 1850.; 16.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/64, no.22 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, August 20, 1850.; 17.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/65 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
      - Chatfield to Mr. Ramirez Director of the State of Nicaragua, Zacapa, Abstract, enclosure to Foreign Office 15/65., July 12, 1850.; 1.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, September 13, 1850.; 18.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/65, no.72 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, December 2, 1850.; 19.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/66, no.109 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, December 13, 1850.; 20.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/66, no.114 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield to Palmerston, April 16, 1851.; 21.; 6pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/70, no.42 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Foster to Chatfield, British Vice Consulate Realejo, December 31, 1850.; 22.; 9pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/70 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield. Mr. Chatfield's no.16 of, January 28, 1850.; 23.; (Copy, photostat, of Foreign Office 15/64 - 8.5 × 11.75 paper). 2pp. (Box 2)
    - Chatfield. Mr. Chatfield's of, February 12, 1850.; 24.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of Foreign Office 15/64, B - 8.5 × 11.75 paper). (Box 2)
    - Chatfield. Mr. Chatfield's no.22 of, March 2, 1850.; 25.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of Foreign Office 15/64, C - 8.5 × 11.75 paper). (Box 2)
  - 36. Christie
    - Christie, W.W. to [Unknown]. St. John, Mosquito [?], September 5, 1848.; 1.; 14pp. (Copy, photostat, of Foreign Office 53/11, A.- 8.5 × 14 paper). (Box 3)
    - Christie to Calvo, San Jose, October 16, 1848.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 97/88 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Christie to Palmerston, San Jose, October 19, 1848.; 3.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of extracts from Foreign Office 97/88 no.14). (Box 3)
    - Christie to Palmerston, Grey Town, March 27, 1849.; 4.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 53/17, no.13 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Christie to Palmerston, Grey Town, April 7, 1849.; 5.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 53/17, no.14 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
  - 37. Clarendon
    - Clarendon to Wyke, Foreign Office, October 31, 1854.; 1.; 8pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/82, no.14 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Clarendon to Wyke, Foreign Office, January 19, 1854.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/82 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Clarendon to Crampton, Foreign Office, February 2, 1854.; 3.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/590, no.20 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Clarendon to Crampton, Foreign Office, February 10, 1854.; 4.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/590, no.31 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Clarendon to Crampton, Foreign Office, August 16, 1855.; 5.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/617, no.175 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Clarendon to Crampton, Foreign Office, November 10, 1855.; 6.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/618, no.259 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Clarendon to Napier, Foreign Office, July 9, 1857.; 7.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/668, no.176 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Clarendon to Ouseley, October 30, 1857.; 8.; 18pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 97/90, no.2 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
  - 38. Clarke
    - Clarke [Geo.]? to E. George Squier, San Jose, October 23, 1849.; 1.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers. 8.5 × 11.75 paper). (Box 3)
    - Clarke, [Francis?] to George Squier, San Jose, September 5, 1849.; 2.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.5 × 11.75 paper). (Box 3)
  - 39. Clayton
    - [Clayton] to [Unknown].D.S.W, April 22, 1850.; 1.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers(?) - 8.5 × 11.75 paper).
    - Clayton, J.M. to Honorable Abbott Lawrence. Washington, December 26, 1849.; 2.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers(?) - 8.5 × 11.75 paper).
    - Clayton, John M. to the Right Honorable Sir H.L. Bulwer. Washington, February 15, 1850.; 3.; 6pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers(?) - 8.5 × 11.75 paper).
    - C[layton], J.M. to [H.L. Bulwer]. Washington, February 11, 1850.; 4.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers(?) - 8.5 × 11.75 paper).
      - Fisher Geo.P. Statement. Washington, March 6, 1856.; 1.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers(?) - 8.5 × 11.75 paper).
    - Lawrence, Abbott to the Honorable John M. Clayton, London, November 15, 1849.; 5.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. -, Clayton Papers(?) - 8.5 × 11.75 paper).
  - 40. Crampton
    - Crampton to Palmerston, Washington, April 2, 1848.; 1.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/485, no.35 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Palmerston. Washington, May 8, 1848.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/485, no.56. - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Palmerston, Washington, May 22, 1848.; 3.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/485, no.62 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Palmerston, Washington, May 22, 1848.; 4.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/485, no.63 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Palmerston. Washington, November 6, 1848.; 5.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/487, no.124 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton, Memo., November 6, 1848.; 6.; (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/487, no.124 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). 1p. (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Palmerston, Washington, November 6, 1848.; 7.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/487, no.127 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Palmerston, Washington, December 18, 1848.; 8.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/487, no.139 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Palmerston, Washington, April 2, 1849.; 9.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/499, no.36 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Palmerston. Washington, June 25, 1849.; 10.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of extract from Foreign Office 5/499 no.61 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Palmerston. Washington, July 23, 1849.; 11.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/500 no.68 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Palmerston. Washington, October 15, 1849.; 12.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/501 no.89 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Palmerston, Washington, December 2, 1849.; 13.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/501, no.104 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Malmesbury. Washington, November 21, 1852.; 14.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/548, no.189 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Malmesbury. Washington, January 2, 1853.; 15.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/563 no.3 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Malmesbury. Washington, January 16, 1853.; 16.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/563 no.18. - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Russell. Washington, January 30, 1853.; 17.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/563 no.29 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - [Crampton]. Washington, Extract., March 13, 1853.; 18.; 2pp. Foreign Office 5/564, no.62 - 7 × 9 red margin paper) (typewritten). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Clarendon. Washington, October 31, 1853.; 19.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/547, no.175 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Clarendon. Washington, January 23, 1854.; 20.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/593 no.17 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Clarendon. Washington, March 6, 1854.; 21.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/594, no.53 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Clarendon. Washington, March 6, 1854.; 22.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/594, no.58 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Clarendon. Washington, September 18, 1854.; 23.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of extract from Foreign Office 5/598, no.229 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Clarendon. Washington, October 9, 1854.; 24.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/599 no.241 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton, John F. to the Right Honorable The Earl of Clarendon, Washington, June 18, 1855.; 25.; 7pp. (Copy, photostat, of Foreign Office 5/621, no.124 - 8.5 × 14 paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton, John F. to the Earl of Clarendon. Washington, October 21, 1855.; 26.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of Foreign Office 5/623 no.227 - 8.5 × 14 paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Clarendon. Washington, March 31, 1856.; 27.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/642, no.75 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
  - 41. Dallas
    - Note., 1.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 3)
    - Dallas to Marcy, March 21, 1856.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S. D, - March 21/56. no.2). (Box 3)
    - Brown, William to [Unknown]., 3.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D.). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to Brown. Morley's Hotel, March 19, 1856.; 4.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. - March 19, 1856). (Box 3)
    - Dallas to Marcy, March 28, 1856.; 5.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. - March 28, 1856) no.3. (Box 3)
    - Brown, William to [Unknown]., 6.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D.). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to [Unknown]. London, March 23, 1856.; 7.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. - March 23, 1856). (Box 3)
    - Dallas to Marcy, April 29, 1856.; 8.; 8pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. - April 29, 1856) no.7. (Box 3)
    - Dallas to Marcy, May 23, 1856.; 9.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. - May 23/56.) no.10. (Box 3)
    - Dallas to Marcy, May 27, 1856.; 10.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. - no.11). (Box 3)
    - Dallas to Marcy, May 30, 1856.; 11.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. no.12). (Box 3)
    - Dallas to Marcy, June 3, 1856.; 12.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D.). no.13. (Box 3)
    - Squier to Dallas, May 28, 1856.; 13.; 4pp. (Copy,typewritten, of S.D. - May 28, 1856). (Box 3)
    - Dallas to Squier, June 1, 1856.; 14.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department). (Box 3)
    - Dallas to Marcy, June 13, 1856.; 15.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. - June 13, 1856) no.15. (Box 3)
    - Dallas to Marcy, July 1, 1856.; 16.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. - July 1, 1856) no.18). (Box 3)
    - Dallas to Marcy, July 11, 1856.; 17.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. - July 11, 1856) no.19. (Box 3)
    - Proposed Article., 18.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. - Article). (Box 3)
    - [Unknown] to [Unknown], March 30, 1856.; 19.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Marcy Papers - 8.25 × 11.75). (Box 3)
  - 42. Gliddon
    - Gliddon to Honorable E. George Squier. Terran, November 4, 1855.; 1.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75). (Box 3)
    - Gliddon to Honorable E. George Squier. London, November 10, 1855.; 2.; 5pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75). (Box 3)
    - Gliddon to Honorable E. George Squier, November 19, 1855.; 3.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75). (Box 3)
    - Gliddon to Honorable E. George Squier, November 29, 1855.; 4.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75). (Box 3)
    - Gliddon to Honorable E. George Squier, January 25, 1856.; 5.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75). (Box 3)
  - 43. Holland
    - Holland, Honorable E. George Squier. 35 Albemarle Street, March 25, 1859.; 1.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75). (Box 3)
    - Holland, G. to Squier. U.S. Consulate, London, April 1, 1859.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75). (Box 3)
    - Holland to Squier. 35 Albermarle Street, April 29, 1859.; 3.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75). (Box 3)